<!-- Title & Breadcrumbs -->
<nav class="navbar">
    <div class="navbar-brand">
        <h1 class="title">World History</h1>
    </div>
    <div class="navbar-end">
        <nav class="breadcrumb is-right nav-breadcrumb">
            <ul>
                <li class="is-active"><a><i class="fa fa-university" aria-hidden="true"></i>&nbsp;World History</a></li>
            </ul>
        </nav>
    </div>
</nav>

    In 2016, with the influence and support of major corporations and foreign bodies NSW Premier Mike Baird was able to implement laws prohibiting environmental protests.<br>
    This opened a path to unprecedented environmental destruction and severe corruption, along with a more authoritative government.<br>
    Corporations were able to increase their influence and they bought out many groups to further their causes, as did many politicians. With society so corrupt, crime became more prominent as politicians funded crime groups to further their policies.<br><br>

    This surge in the power of the upper class, led to the mass development of Sydney’s urban center and in a push for urban consolidation much of Sydney’s urban sprawl was demolished, forcing those people into the inner city and freeing up land for industrial construction.<br>
    These people forced into the city contributed to a much higher poverty rate and worsened crime. At first, Sydney’s police struggled to cope under the growing pressure but they were aided by new technologies and increased militarisation.<br><br>

    Then, when Donald Trump won the American election he took advantage of Australia’s newfound instability and close relationship to the USA. Most significantly he pressured the Australian government to discriminate against the Asian population, phasing in a new White Australia Policy.<br>
    Trump also sent US troops to Australia to enforce his will and establish further US power there.<br>
    As a result, many of Sydney’s Asians left the country, fearing for their welfare and lots more moved to Chinatown, which became a refuge for many Asians.<br><br>

    Now Sydney is a city consumed by it’s own greed, where extreme wealth lies right alongside extreme poverty. Crime and disorder are common as oppression and misfortune plagues many of the city’s residents, overwhelmed by their sudden fall from grace. Corrupt, selfish and indecisive, few politicians or leaders have risen to the challenge and Sydney spirals further down into anarchy.<br><br>
    <script src="../js/script.js"></script>
