<nav class="navbar">
    <div class="navbar-brand">
        <h1 class="title">Silver Spectre - Hugo Johannsen</h1>
    </div>
    <div class="navbar-end">
        <nav class="breadcrumb is-right nav-breadcrumb">
            <ul>
                <li><a class=" link-page link-page-home"><span><img class="image is-16x16" src="img/icon/icon.png"></span>&nbsp;Vigilantes</a></li>
                    <li><a class=" link-page link-page-heroes"><i class="fa fa-address-book-o" aria-hidden="true"></i>&nbsp;Sub-Universes</a></li>
                    <li><a class=" link-page link-page-viper"><i class="fa fa-address-book-o" aria-hidden="true"></i>&nbsp;Silver Spectre</a></li>
                    <li class="is-active"><a class=" link-page link-page-viper-viper"><i class="fa fa-user"></i>&nbsp;Silver Spectre</a></li>
                    </ul>
                </nav>
            </div>
        </nav><br><br>
    <div class="columns is-mobile">
        <div class="column is-two-thirds">

            <blockquote>"I have never yet heard of a murderer who was not afraid of a ghost"</blockquote>

            Hugo had dreamed of being a superhero since his childhood so when he saw an infomercial promising ‘amazing physical abilities with which to impress your peers’ he leapt at the chance, signing up despite warnings from his friends and family.<br><br>

            He was accepted and sent to a facility owned by the corporation, ExoCorp. Here he underwent tests and experiments for a while with no success. Hugo was disappointed and deemed the endeavour hopeless, deciding to stop attending his sessions. After not turning up for several appointments some of the Velvet Knights arrived at his home and forcibly detained him, returning Hugo to ExoCorp, where his captors claimed he was too important to be allowed to leave.<br><br>

            Hugo was angry with himself for being tricked and resolved to be uncooperative with the scientists. As a result they drugged him and the rest of his time in the facility passed as a blur.<br>
            Eventually Hugo awoke in a room, alone but for Phillip Dean, the owner of ExoCorp, and as he came to was shocked to discover he had no physical form. He was startled but elated, figuring it was his promised ability. That was until he was told that so far the process had been irreversible at which point he flipped and tried and tried to get away. For some reason he was unable to escape and Dean eventually managed to calm him down, explaining that they believed the trigger was a mental process. Hugo concentrated hard and managed to revert to a tangible state.<br><br>
            <div class="drop-down-box" id="spectre">
                Dean then began to tell Hugo how amazing this power was and how beneficial it could be.<br>
                He learnt that the Dean’s plan was to keep him captive, in order to test more, ensuring it was viable, then distribute the technology globally with the goal of bettering society.
                Despite his apparent goodwill Hugo was disagreeable, not wanting to be tricked again or have his power lost in further experimentation so when a commotion erupted in another ward he seized the opportunity to escape, this time succeeding.<br>
                After successfully escaping he decided that it would be best to keep what had happened secret, so that people don’t know about the technology and don’t flock to the corporation wanting superpowers of their own.<br>
                Hugo also decided that he might as well become the superhero he had wanted to be so he snuck back into ExoCorp and stole the suit designed for him.<br>
                With this he became the Silver Spectre and began his campaign to stop the work of ExoCorp.
                </div>
                <div style="width: 100%; height: 20px; border-bottom: 1px solid black; text-align: center">
                    <span style="background-color:#fff;">
                        <a class="icon is-large" style="position: relative; bottom: 2px; background-color: white;">
                            <i id="spectre" class="drop-down-button fa fa-arrow-circle-down" aria-hidden="true"></i>
                        </a>
                    </span>
                </div><br><br><br>

                <h4 class="subtitle">Arsenal</h4>
                <ul>
                    <li>Silver Spectre costume</li>
                    <li>
                        Shock gloves
                        <ul>
                            <li>Can deliver an electric shock from the palm generated by minute batteries in the glove.</li>
                            <li>Charging the gloves by proximity to each other can increase the charge generated and allowing Hugo to produce an EMP like blast if the gloves are then quickly separated.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul><br>

                <h4 class="subtitle">Capabilities</h4>
                <ul>
                    <li>Intangibility<br>
                        <ul>
                            <li>The ability to dispel his physical form, allowing objects to pass through him without resistance.</li>
                            <li>He is unable to pass through objects with a very high density (roughly 13kg/m3). E.g. Mercury, Tantalum, Uranium, Tungsten, Gold, Plutonium, Platinum, Iridium and Osmium.</li>
                            <li> If dense materials enter the body they limit the strength of his ability.</li>
                            <li>Some things cannot be tunnelled through if they are too large (exceeding a limit in width or height).</li>
                            <li>Can mentally control which parts of his body become intangible and when.</li>
                        </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li>Stealth<br>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Able to move quite quietly and discreetly</li>
                            </ul>

                            </li>
                            </ul><br>

                        <h4 class="subtitle">Qualities</h4>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Compassionate</li>
                            <li>Courageous</li>
                            <li>Somewhat slow</li>
                            <li>Naïve</li>
                            <li>Touchy</li>
                        </ul>
                        </div>

                        <div class="column">
                            <img width="400px" height="500px" src="img/character-art/spectre.png" alt="Image"><br><br>
                                <article class="message is-primary">
                                    <div class="message-header">
                                        Silver Spectre costume
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="message-body">
                                        <ul class="img-caption-body">
                                            <li>Made of a combination of carbon fibre and UHMWPE making it flexible and very protective, even very resistant to corrosion, abrasion, water, chemicals, UV radiation and microorganisms.</li>
                                            <li>Grey trench coat.</li>
                                            <li>Black combat boots.</li>
                                            <li>Black shock gloves</li>
                                        </ul>
                                    </div>
                                </article>
                                <article class="message is-primary">
                                    <div class="message-header">
                                        Extra Resources
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="message-body">
                                        <i>Some additional links and comments to help appreciate Silver Spectre:</i><br><br>
                                        <h5 class="subtitle">Notes</h5>
                                        <ul class="img-caption-body">
                                            <li>The Silver Spectre has the very best intentions and only wants to do something for the greater good, but the world, especially the one he enters into, is much more horrifying and complex than he ever imagined. His story is that of overcoming his ignorance and inability, maintaining hope and resolve against failure and chaos.</li>
                                            <li>The Silver Spectre is also symbolic of a ghost, haunting people for their crimes.</li>
                                            <li>The idea of a Shakespearean fatal flaw is drawn upon in his naivety, and reflected in the styling of his story as a tragedy.</li>
                                            <li>He is a beacon of light in a city of darkness.</li>
                                        </ul>
                                        </div>
                                        </article>
                                    </div>
                                    </div>
                                <script src="../js/script.js"></script>
