<!-- Title & Breadcrumbs -->
<nav class="navbar">
    <div class="navbar-brand">
        <h1 class="title">Lóngyǐng 龙影</h1>
    </div>
    <div class="navbar-end">
        <nav class="breadcrumb is-right nav-breadcrumb">
            <ul>
                    <li><a class=" link-page link-page-heroes"><i class="fa fa-address-book-o" aria-hidden="true"></i>&nbsp;Sub-Universes</a></li>
                    <li><a class=" link-page link-page-viper"><i class="fa fa-address-book-o" aria-hidden="true"></i>&nbsp;Viper</a></li>
                    <li class="is-active"><a class=" link-page link-page-viper-jp"><i class="fa fa-users" aria-hidden="true"></i>&nbsp;Lóngyǐng 龙影</a></li>
                    </ul>
                </nav>
            </div>
        </nav>
    <div class="columns is-mobile">
        <div class="column is-two-thirds">
            <blockquote>"Our greatest glory is not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall."</blockquote>

            With a name translating to ‘Shadow Dragon’, the Longying are an underground group of traditional Chinese warriors. They seek to liberate the Chinese population of Sydney.<br><br>
            Originally the group was small and based in a building near Darling Harbour but US forces discovered them and raided their base, killing many members and destroying important documents and items.
            Some Longying survived and moved to Paddy’s Market, which they were able to buy after securing a great sum of money from associates overseas. A secret underground level was built and here the Longying train in ancient weapons and martial arts.<br><br>
            They have a system of underground tunnels that link Paddy’s Market to a number of Longying controlled venues across the area, including laundromats and yum-cha restaurants.<br><br>
            They now have a strong influence in Chinatown but have escaped government attention, preferring to continue building their forces in secret. They have gained many followers and have some very well trained warriors.<br><br>
            Led by a council of elders, they have traditional practices and beliefs, following the teachings of Confucius.

            <br><br>

                <h4 class="subtitle">Weaponry</h4>
                <ul>
                    <li>Gun (staff)</li>
                    <li>Jian (sword)</li>
                    <li>Hook sword</li>
                    <li>Rope dart</li>
                    <li>Chinese archery</li>
                    <li>Chinese martial arts</li>
                </ul><br>

                <h4 class="subtitle">Notable Members:</h4>
                <ul>
                    <li>Viper
                        <ul>
                            <li>While no longer as strongly affiliated with Longying, Viper was trained by them and maintains good relations by helping the group regularly.</li>
                            <li>He is a very passionate supporter of theirs but sometimes disagrees with their actions and beliefs.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Tongyi Shen
                        <ul>
                            <li>A close friend of Viper</li>
                            <li>He runs a large and successful yum-cha restaurant outside of Chinatown.</li>
                            <li>This restaurant serves as a base for the Longying and is linked to their passages.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>Jonathan Pan
                        <ul>
                            <li>Came to the Longying with Viper and Tongyi</li>
                            <li>He is committed wholly to the group and trains extensively.</li>
                            <li>He is now on the council of elders and one of the best warriors they have.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul><br>

                <h4 class="subtitle">Base</h4>
                The Paddy’s Market building has been redesigned with a more Oriental theme. The ground floor is a permanent marketplace (many shop-owners are Longying and may sleep in hammocks etc. behind the storefront) while the floor above is a storeroom.<br>
                Behind an ornate door guarded by warriors is a staircase leading down to the underground level. This level has many rooms such as training areas, dormitories, armouries and meeting areas.<br>Furthermore, secure doors guarded by warriors allow access to the underground tunnels that lead between bases.
                </div>

                <div class="hidden">
                    <img width="400px" height="500px" src="" alt="Image"><br><br>
                        <article class="message is-primary">
                            <div class="message-header">
                                BraveHelm Alpha
                            </div>
                            <div class="message-body">
                                A military helmet developed by DARPA, the BraveHelm is worn by soldiers and influences their brains: reducing stress, keeping focus and reducing pain by using transcranial pulsed ultrasound waves.<br><br>

                                However, magnetic nanoparticles (surgically implanted and heated by magnetic fields) are also discreetly used in conjunction with the BraveHelm, allowing for near-complete control of a soldier’s actions.<br>
                                The BraveHelm Alpha controls this, essentially giving the user mind control over soldiers under their command.<br><br>

                                The BraveHelm is black in colour and has a sliding face guard, allowing protection of the entire head. It is fairly bulky and noticeably geometric in shape. A narrow slit between the faceplate and the head guard allows the soldier to see.<br><br>
                                The BraveHelm Alpha is similar but has a glowing red alpha symbol roughly above the ears.
                                </div>
                                </article>
                                <article class="message is-primary">
                                    <div class="message-header">
                                        Extra Resources
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="message-body">
                                        <i>Some additional links and comments to help appreciate Major Patton:</i><br><br>
                                        <h5 class="subtitle">Notes</h5>
                                        <ul class="img-caption-body">
                                            <li>A major aspect of Patton is his passion for AFL. It acts as a very humanising and relatable feature of this otherwise complex character and alludes to the tight relationship between sport and the military, a major theme for Patton.</li>
                                        </ul>
                                        </div>
                                        </article>
                                    </div>
                                    </div>
                                <script src="../js/script.js"></script>
